Excuse me, sir.
Sir, I have a question for you.
How did you get rich, sir?
Sir, I grew a channel to
20 million followers in the United States.
I asked people for advice to help the younger generation.
Can I be in film?
Yes, sir.
Okay.
My one piece of advice is this.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, how did you get rich?
I got rich by having an idea
in my head of making it real.
I built a company called Fluid
and I sold the pricewaterhousecooper for
more money than I'll ever need.
How much money are you worth today?
Three, four hundred million.
I've brought the company up to 150 million.
And we're scaling that.
Yeah, we're scaling that consistently.
I think 30 million.
30 million dollars?
Yes.
What was the lowest point in your life?
The lowest point in my
life was losing 55 million overnight
and I was shell-shocked.
You said overnight?
Literally overnight. The recession happened.
How you doing?
Hi.
Lads, I said we really enjoyed the interview yesterday.
Oh yeah?
Would you lads come and join
us for a glass of champagne?
Yeah, we'll come in there for a second.
Yeah, yeah.
Give me a lesson about business
right here in our time in school.
How did you scale a 100 million dollar company?
So the secret, the thing
they don't really educate you on,
they don't really announce, they probably
keep it to one side is
if me and you died tomorrow
and you had one more message
to leave with the younger generation,
what would that be?
Wow.
Um...
I think...
Guys, we just landed in London,
one of the richest cities in the entire world.
This is a place where billionaires are everywhere
and I just flew from across
the world, from the United States,
to be here with one mission.
To meet and interview the richest people in London
and ask them exactly how they built their fortunes,
their million dollar, their billion dollar net worth,
and how you can do the exact same thing
and become financially free in today's world.
So this video
is about to be insane from start to finish.
So stay tuned.
With that being said, let's
get this video on the way.
Guys, we're headed in right now to the
city of London to go get our first interview.
But we just found something out insane.
Guys, London ranks number six as
the wealthiest city in the entire world.
There's over 210,000 millionaires that live here.
And it's home to some of
the most powerful billionaires on planet Earth.
So honestly, who knows who we're
going to go find out here.
Let's go find out.
Excuse me, sir.
I had a question for you.
How did you get rich?
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
How did you get rich?
Sorry?
Sir.
How did you get rich?
No, don't bother.
Okay.
I got you.
Don't bother.
Excuse me, sir.
How did you become wealthy?
Question for you.
How did you get rich?
What were you saying?
Don't bother.
I'm not so easy in England, too.
Hey, it's not that easy, but we
don't stop until we get them to-
It's a family nation.
I like it.
Absolutely, man.
Nice to meet you, man.
I watch you all the time.
Do you actually?
Absolutely.
Thank you, man.
I appreciate that.
Interviewing all the wealthy people and getting
connections and all the rest of it.
Hey, we're going to find some billionaires right now.
They're here.
But they're very low key.
They're very low key.
Yes, sir.
I appreciate that, my man.
Thank you.
You're very welcome.
Take care.
Thank you, sir.
Appreciate it.
All right, you guys.
I'm going to go to some states like
Texas or Florida where everybody's down to talk
to you, man.
These people are private.
They're secretive.
They're going from meeting to meeting.
They are gate keeping out here.
But look, I didn't fly all the way
across the world to London for nothing, you guys.
So I'm not going to stop until I
get these millionaires and billionaires to give us the
game for you and the younger generation.
Let's go see what they have to say.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir.
I have a question for you.
How did you get rich, sir?
Sir, I grew a channel to
20 million followers in the United States.
I asked people for advice to help the younger generation.
Do you have one piece of advice for
the younger generation to help them be successful and
in today's world?
Am I being filmed?
Yes, sir.
Okay.
My one piece of advice is this.
You don't get rich by working for someone else.
You don't get rich by being paid a salary.
You don't get rich by starting your own business.
You slave your guts out night
and day meeting cash flow crises.
You get rich by selling your business.
So my advice to someone who
wants to get rich, start a business.
Build it up for a couple
of years and then sell it.
What type of company did you sell?
Real quick, sir.
Sir.
So I've interviewed John Caldwell.
I've interviewed...
Let me show you my channel.
I've done stuff with like Tom Cruise.
Are you happy with what I said?
I'm happy with the answer, but sir, I
promise you it's not enough for a clip.
You mentioned selling a business.
What's the number one thing that
entrepreneurs get wrong about the exit?
First of all, when you start a business,
you should work out at the very beginning who's
going to buy it in four years time.
How do you identify the buyers?
Because you're in a business and
you're starting up a company doing something.
It might be advertising.
It might be public relations.
You can work out which of the big
firms might want to buy your successful little company
in a few years time.
Identify them at the outset.
And then everything you do is given.
Okay.
So you're geared towards making that sale in the end.
Now what's this for?
What was the main company that you had sold, sir?
I'm not telling you.
Can I show you what it's for, sir, at least?
Before you go in there, I at
least want to show you the channel.
Do you know Tom Cruise?
Yes.
So this is me and him.
What industry did you design?
Let me ask you, sir.
What was the best advice that
you ever received throughout your career?
If there's one lesson...
No more.
Give me one more.
I'm a huge fan of your channel.
Have you seen it before?
I've seen it before.
Oh, okay, okay.
Sir, one more.
You're not going to get more.
What's that?
You're not going to get more out there.
You've got to go.
Look, man, I pressed him probably about as
much as I could press anybody that you see
me do on this channel, you guys.
Nonetheless, man, he said it right there, man.
He said, you're not going to
get rich working for somebody else.
You've got to start your own business, identify
the right buyer, and sell that thing, you
guys.
Crazy interview out here in London, man.
If this is how it's going to
go, man, let's keep it rolling, you guys.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, how did you get rich?
I'm just interviewing someone right now.
How did you get rich?
I got rich by having an idea
in my head and making it real.
I built a company called Fluid out of
Hong Kong, and I sold it to PricewaterhouseCooper
for more money than I made.
I never need.
How much money are you worth today?
Three, four hundred million.
Are you serious?
I'm going all over London interviewing the
richest people to help the younger generation.
Can I get a minute with
you for the channel real quick?
Yeah, of course.
Let me ask you this real quick.
You've interviewed tons of people, and
you've asked them this one question.
What is your dream?
Excuse me, get off the phone.
I've got something important to ask you.
What am I going to ask you?
You're going to ask me how I got rich?
What's my dream?
Exactly.
I'm going to ask you how
you got rich and what's your dream.
Let's do both.
So I interview billionaires for a living.
You haven't interviewed me yet.
I'm a bit insulted.
We've got to make it happen at some point.
What is your dream?
My dream is to fix the education system.
I feel like young people in
particular are getting let down right now.
AI is coming, but no one's warning people
that these jobs we keep telling people they're
going to get won't exist.
We're not giving people the knowledge to realize
they can take control of their own f***ing
life.
They have agency over their life.
That's what I want to give people,
and I will not stop until that happens.
Because they're saying that the poor
get poorer and the rich get richer.
What keeps people broke in today's world?
A lot of people are blaming
the rich or they're blaming the government.
They're blaming other people as
to why they're not making it.
The best thing you can do
is blame yourself and skill up.
Realize you can have agency over your life.
That's what I think.
I tried to go the easy route
and get social benefit to help me.
I tried to go the
easy route and get a job.
I had to go the hard route, man.
That was the best thing that ever happened
to me because I realized I can create wealth.
I didn't need anyone to give it to me.
I will f***ing take it.
What do the richest people in
the world do differently from everybody else?
Think about all the billionaires you know.
What do they do differently
from- There's no work-life balance.
The rich don't do two things.
One, they do not think about retirement.
They just think about doing stuff they love every day.
That means you can go forever.
There's no limit at 65 where
you stop, so you just keep going.
The thing is, they're not thinking about
Monday to Friday is work and Saturday, Sunday
is not work.
There is no work-life balance.
It's just life.
I have an eight-year-old son.
He's included in my business.
You only want work-life balance if
you don't enjoy what you do.
What did you have to sacrifice to become this successful?
I have sacrificed the easy life.
I think when people get a salary, they
get trapped on a drug that stops them.
Golden handcuffs, they call it.
It's worse than that.
It's a middle-class trap.
A lot of people let the salary own them.
Once they start getting a
salary, they start building up debt.
If you've got a mortgage, you're working for the bank.
If you've got a car, you're working for the bank.
If you've got a car loan,
you're working for the car company.
I just want to work for myself.
I want to own my time.
The only thing money has brought me
of true value is I own my time.
I'm standing in the street helping this
guy, not because he's not paying me.
You're not paying me, right?
I just can because it's
my time and I own it.
Money only buys you time.
And if you're not spending
money on time, you're wasting money.
You don't need to teach this in school, right?
They don't teach this in school,
in my opinion, for a reason.
Why is that?
If you understood how money
works, why would anyone sell time?
It's limited.
You only have a certain
amount of time in a day.
Why would you sell time as an outcome?
Most of my businesses have been successful.
I've sold outcomes.
I've sold results.
I've taken percentage of what the success was
on that business, not the amount of time
it took me to do it.
The teacher is also charging by the hour.
So the people teaching you
don't even understand how money works.
You know why?
They don't want you to operate in the real world.
They want you to go work for someone else.
Did you have an LLC or
an S-corp when you started your companies?
In England, you have a limited company.
In Hong Kong, similar.
How important is that entity
structure when you're building your business?
Well, of course, you need to make sure that
when you build out a company that you follow
the law.
But it also protects you though.
But of course, if you have
a limited business, same as LLC.
In America, it's harder for you to be sued personally.
And of course, business shouldn't be personal.
As far as in America, I know a
lot of people like to sue each other.
You do need a structure, I think mainly
for your accounts, but also legally to protect
yourself.
A lot of people make a million
excuses as to why they can't start companies.
There's a business that I
use to start all my companies.
It's called Bizzee.
And the most successful entrepreneurs I use,
they use this company and it essentially allows
them to start their business and open it
up overnight as opposed to thinking days, weeks
and months like everybody thinks.
Okay.
What's it called again?
It's called Bizzee.
B-I-Z-E-E.
It helps them structure their businesses.
People should know that.
I love that.
How old are you today?
How old am I today?
I'm 51.
You look damn good for 51.
I feel younger.
Simon, if me and you died tomorrow and you
had one more message to leave with the younger
generation, what would that be?
Purpose of life is a life with purpose.
We get such a short time on this planet.
Don't ever live with regret.
I meet a lot of people in their
80s and 90s who wish they did something.
You don't want to be that.
At least if you try it and
it doesn't work, you've got a good story.
I will always execute on an idea
because I don't want to live with regret.
What if, what if?
Too many people live with regret.
They don't take action and try it.
You've got amazing advice, my friend.
Thank you.
Sorry to interrupt in my interview.
Thank you for all you do for everybody, man.
Oh, no, it's nice of you to say that, man.
Likewise, I love you.
I connect with all the
millionaires and billionaires I interview.
Could I get your contact?
Yeah, yeah, of course, man.
You bet.
Guys, we just interviewed Simon
Squibb out here in London, man.
He's got over 20 million followers across
social media, not to mention, like you said,
he's worth hundreds of millions of dollars.
But did you hear what we talked about?
Look, every single one of these guys,
the millionaires, the billionaires, they all do
one thing the same.
They structure their business properly.
That's what turns an idea into a real company.
And that's exactly why I tell everyone, like
I just told Simon to use my name.
Busy makes it insanely easy to
set up your LLC or escort.
They handle all the paperwork, help protect
your personal assets, and even set you up
the right way for taxes.
So guys, you don't need some crazy lawyer.
You don't need to overthink it.
You can literally get your business set up in minutes.
So guys, waste no more time.
Go down and click the link
in the description of this video.
I'll see you in the next one.
Bye.
Congrats, nice to see you again.
You handled the call.
Welcome back to Busy to set your
business up with Busy and actually start.
That being said, let's go get this next interview.
How you doing?
Hi.
Martin said he really enjoyed the interview yesterday.
Oh yeah?
Would you like to come and
join us for a glass of champagne?
Yeah.
Well, we'll come in there for a second as well.
All right.
dürfen sie, éhm.
Yeah.
A glass of champagne.
How you doing sir?
Gerning Sir.
Nice to see you.
Good to see you.
I now know who you are.
Yeah.
I looked you up.
Straight off.
Nice, nice.
Ready to go?
Yes, I did.
Investors, you take your chances.
As a businessman, you're dependent on your own abilities,
your own skills, your own expertise.
But do you think everybody's built for entrepreneurship?
No, I don't think everybody is,
but nature has a way of
sorting out the ones that are
from the ones that aren't.
And if you discover that it's not for you,
then you can always try something else.
How are you today?
I'm in my 86th year.
You're 86 years old?
I will be this year, yes.
That's incredible, man.
If you were to go back
and talk to your 20-year-old self
and give yourself one piece
of advice, what would that be?
It would be, you won't
believe what you're about to do
in your lifetime.
Wow, so you ended up doing some amazing things.
I would have told my 20-year-old,
get ready for a roller coaster ride.
Do you have any regrets?
Oh, everyone has regrets, of course.
Regrets, I've had a few, but then again,
too few to mention.
Hey, that's a Frank Sinatra right there.
Yesterday, you told me that the way to get rich
in today's world is to sell a company.
Did you ever sell a company?
Yes, you can assume that.
What do people need to understand
when they want to build a company to sell it?
Most business owners' dream is to sell their company,
but a lot of people will never exit a business.
What can you tell people about selling a company?
How do you make that happen?
I'll give you an example.
I think that for some
people, it's the path to success.
Join a firm, learn the
trades for a couple of years,
and then with a colleague or two,
set up your own version using the skills you've acquired
and gradually build it up over a few years.
I mean two or three years.
Acquire yourself a client base, build it up
so you've got a turnover
of half a million, a million,
and then you sell it for a multiple of that.
When you sell the business, you become rich.
You're 86 today.
If me and you died tomorrow
and you had one more message
to leave with the younger generation, what would that be?
If I had one more message for the younger generation,
I'd say,
it's not what fortune throws your way.
It's how you react to whatever comes your way.
It's not the luck.
It's how you respond to whatever luck happens.
My motto, and I think it's the motto
of every one of the people we've been talking about.
In Latin, quod tango muto.
In English, it means that which I touch, I change.
And if you can change the lives of other people
for the better,
then you've achieved something worth remembering.
You have amazing advice, sir.
Thank you for your time, sir.
I really appreciate that.
Guys, so look, I cannot make this up, man.
We go in there and he says,
look, I looked you guys up
on the channel and he comes out
to drop some data for you guys, man.
Let's get this next interview right now.
London is going crazy, you guys.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir.
Question for you.
Huh?
I have a question for you.
Sure.
How did you become wealthy?
How did I become wealthy?
Yes, sir.
Banking.
And baking.
Investment banking.
Where are you from?
Originally from Nigeria, but I grew up here.
London.
Yeah, I went to school in England.
Did you ever own a
company at any point in time
or you just worked in the business world?
I own my own company now.
You own your own company?
Yeah.
What type of business is it?
Fun business.
Actually.
Yeah, like a hedge fund.
You own a hedge fund.
Yeah, that's why I can
dress like this on a weekday.
So what was the most amount of money
that you made in a single year?
I think 30 million.
30 million dollars?
Yes.
Did you come from a rich family?
Relatively.
Relatively rich.
Yeah, not rich, but my father's a doctor,
so middle class.
But you chose not to be a spoiled rich kid.
Yeah, of course.
You got out there to yourself.
You work hard for it.
Yeah, you work hard for it.
Why didn't you want to
be a doctor like your dad?
Two of my brothers ended up being in medicine.
So you're kind of the black sheep of the family.
Totally.
We all have different parts in life.
Take me back to the most life-changing conversation
you ever had.
What's the greatest piece of advice
that you received throughout your career?
Wow.
When someone says no to you,
what they mean is try harder.
I love that.
I always like to say
that no does not mean no.
It just means not yet.
Exactly.
It just means try harder.
I've been to job interviews where,
when I was younger, someone rejected me.
Then the person sitting in the
desk next to him hired me.
Never take no for an answer.
What's more important in the business world today,
what you know or who you know?
I think what you know now.
What you know.
Yeah, but in the past it was who you know.
Why?
Well, because if you think about it,
the governor of the Bank of England was complaining
that his daughter doesn't have a job.
That wouldn't happen 20 years ago.
Because nepotism, yeah, that person would have got a job.
So what is a lesson about money
that banks don't want people to know?
The bank multiplier.
Every pound you deposit in the bank,
the bank lends it nine times.
Hey, they don't teach you that in school.
They don't teach you that in school.
Did you ever leverage money?
Of course, yeah, that's the only way to make money.
You have to leverage.
And I did an MBA.
No one told me that the
power of wealth is about leverage.
All these properties you see here, someone's leveraging.
Everything you see around here, even this car, is leveraged.
Are you married?
Yes, I am. Yeah.
Married with two great kids.
For how long have you been married?
Oh, I've been with my wife 30-something years.
How long have you been faithful?
30-something years.
Always, always.
And your kids, how old are they today?
Oh, they're 21 and 18.
How old are you?
I'm old.
You're old?
I'm older than I look.
Older than 50?
Yes.
No, just, I'm around 58.
So if me and you died tomorrow,
and you had one more message to leave
with the younger generation, what would that be?
The US has only been around for 300 years.
And look at what they've achieved.
When the queen died, the queen had been alive
for a third of the existence of the US.
So get out there.
The world is big.
Compounding helps you.
Whatever investment you make now,
your children are never ever going to say
you made a bad investment.
So don't sit there worrying
about whether you pay 10% more
or not.
Get in, and I think in 20, 30 years time,
you're never going to regret it.
Can I tell you something, sir?
Sure.
You have incredible advice.
Well, we try.
Thank you so much for
your time, and I appreciate that.
Guys, I can't make that up.
Look, I saw my guy across the street,
and I just had a feeling, man,
that he had some sneaky wealth.
$30 million in a single year, man,
in the money business, in finance,
and he just gave us the blueprint right there.
The richest people in the world,
man, they leverage money.
He said, look at the car, look at the house,
look at the restaurant, everything out here, man.
Crazy game, crazy good interview.
Let's go get this next one
out here in London, you guys.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, how did you get rich?
How did I get rich?
I made my first million at 23.
What line of business are you in, man?
So now I'm in health tech.
I'm a founder of a health tech company.
What was the most amount of money
that you made in a single year?
I brought the company up to $150 million,
and we're scaling that.
$150 million.
Yeah, we're scaling that consistently.
Can I interview you for a minute?
I go all over the world interviewing billionaires
to help the younger generation.
Is that OK?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah.
What was the lowest point in your life?
The lowest point in my
life was losing $55 million overnight,
and I was shell-shocked.
You used it overnight?
Literally overnight.
The recession happened.
The banks foreclosed on all of our facilities.
We had three massive developments.
They just withdrew all of that.
And that was good.
Are you serious?
Yeah, and that was good because I was getting arrogant.
I had win after win after win.
I was quite young.
And I thought I was a god.
I thought I was invincible.
And my character was altering.
And the lesson I learned from that was the universe,
if you don't contribute, the universe
will take it away from you
because you need to give back.
So though I helped my family, I wasn't really
conscious of the larger population.
I wasn't really kind of helping and being
of value to the universe.
So the universe was like,
I'm going to put you back
to where you started, and you're going
to have to prove that you're deserving.
How old are you today?
I'm 51 today.
Yeah.
You're in incredible shape.
How important was your physical fitness
for your financial success?
Is there a correlation there?
So here's the thing.
Subconsciously, people might not like to hear this,
but when you sit there, it commands
an element of respect.
I was very young when I made my first millions.
And I had the chairman of Bank of Scotland.
Yeah.
And I was very young
when I made my first millions.
And I had the chairman
of Bank of Scotland, et cetera.
And they kind of stepped backward from their position
and let me put across what I needed to.
And there was an element of respect, you know?
And when you walk into
a place, people will notice you.
They'll want to speak to you.
It's just a fact.
You're a part of the
top 1% of the top 1%.
What is the secret that the wealthiest people know
that 99% of people do not know?
Everyone knows the formula, but they can't execute it.
You have to be continually focused.
Ideas are cheap.
Everyone can.
Some people I know have fantastic ideas,
and they're much more capable than me.
They're much more naturally gifted,
but they won't put the world
into the hands of the people who are working.
You take action.
I take action, and I
have the stomach for the sacrifice.
Did you go to university?
Yeah, I read law at university.
People don't believe that, but I read law, yeah.
Give me a lesson about business right here,
not time school.
How did you scale a $100 million company?
So the secret, the thing
they don't really educate you on,
they don't really announce,
they probably keep it to one side,
and I didn't know this until I started health tech,
is annual recurring revenues.
If I'm selling this bag, I've got to sell that.
And I might sell 10,000 this week,
but next week I might sell-
You go out and find the deal.
Yeah, but when you're having something
that has a subscription base,
that money is compounded all the time.
You're making that money.
You've got 5,000 subscribers.
You're bringing X amount of income.
You leverage AI.
You leverage marketing.
You increase that.
That money's coming in whilst you sleep.
Every month.
And it's compounding.
And also, key to that is
that institutions will look at that
and they will multiply that by 10 or 20,
and that's how they value your company.
So you can get a very high evaluation
based on a much smaller revenue.
They say that the double R on the Rolls Royce
stands for recurring revenue.
Exactly.
You're 51 years old today.
51, yeah, yeah, yeah.
If me and you died tomorrow,
and you had one more minute,
and you had a message to leave
with the younger generation,
what would that be?
Go for it.
Stop stalling.
Stop waiting.
Stop self-doubting.
People less competent, less creative, less talented
than you have made it, stop hesitating.
Just go for it.
Jump today.
You have incredible advice, sir.
Thank you so much.
That's a wrap on today's video, man.
London was incredible.
I got no words.
The millionaires and the billionaires
just dropped so much game.
So I need you guys to stop right now,
like and subscribe for amazing content
coming every week with the richest people in the world
and all the business owners you can ever imagine, guys.
If you want to connect with and get direct access
to the eight, nine, and 10-figure entrepreneurs
that you see me interview every week on this channel,
guys, go down, click the link in the description
of this video to join the School of Mentors,
which is the number one most powerful entrepreneur community
and network in the entire world,
where I host live calls every single week
with the millionaires and the billionaires
that I interview.
So I can't wait to see you on the inside.
With that being said, I'll
see you in the next video.